{
    "subject": "resource/Oliver_Thornton",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Musical_theatre",
    "human_readable": "Oliver Thornton's genre is Musical theatre.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9302905201911926,
            "question": "Is Oliver Thornton associated with musicals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8502671122550964,
            "question": "What kind of music does Oliver Thornton perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8425812125205994,
            "question": "Does Oliver Thornton work in dramatic theatre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8251791596412659,
            "question": "What genre of performance is Oliver Thornton known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8073622584342957,
            "question": "What is the musical style frequently featured in Oliver Thornton's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7680367231369019,
            "question": "What is Oliver Thornton's area of expertise in the performing arts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6088486313819885,
            "question": "What kind of stories are often told in Oliver Thornton's performances?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5318670868873596,
            "question": "What type of shows does Oliver Thornton typically work in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3805532455444336,
            "question": "In which artistic discipline does Oliver Thornton excel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32762664556503296,
            "question": "What is Oliver Thornton's primary creative output?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Oliver Thornton's genre is Musical theatre.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6670_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which artistic discipline does Oliver Thornton excel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6670_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of shows does Oliver Thornton typically work in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6670_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of stories are often told in Oliver Thornton's performances?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6670_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6670_45.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to the documents, Oliver Thornton has a career in musicals and has appeared in various big, blockbuster musicals such as Priscilla Queen of the Desert, Les Mis\u00e9rables, Phantom Of The Opera, and The Rocky Horror Show."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Oliver Thornton's career in musical theater, which supports the statement that his genre is musical theatre."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}